Li Xiao.
Haven't you always wanted to see the true god?
Let me show you.
I originally wanted to use you
to lure your father out
to face the truth from twenty years ago with Mei Yuanhe.
Too bad his time was up,
so you'll have to see it for him.
Young Master
That lock...
Isn't that...
Father... Mother...
Is that you?
What did you say?
They're all Dragon-Seeking Clan members who died here twenty years ago.
Please!
Spare me!
I beg you!
It really appeared!
I'm begging you!
Spare me!
Lord Evil God!
Once you leave the tomb,
everyone will surely submit to you!
I will be your most loyal servant.
Spare me! Spare the Mei family!
I beg you!
Please! Spare the Mei family!
Lord Evil God!
What are they worshipping?
I don't know.
Isn't it empty?
There's nothing there.
Please! Spare the Mei family!
What's wrong, Chun'er?
Mei.
I can't leave.
My brother is still inside.
My father is inside too.
Let's go back together.
I haven't given him the divorce papers yet.
Brother!
Jinzi!
Something's wrong with him.
What's wrong with him?
Brother!
Brother, what's wrong?
I want more gold!
Brother!
Chun'er!
And you said there were no evil spirits.
I think they look a lot like evil spirits.
They've completely lost their minds now.
I'm afraid in their eyes,
we've both turned into some kind of treasure.
Rat,
did you bring silver needles?
I did.
Get ready to pierce the Baihui point on top of their heads.
To keep them awake.
I still need to question them.
Okay.
Father,
you're here too.
That's wonderful.
Father, your son is about to dominate the world.
I'll use the Evil Entity to achieve great things!
I know.
My achievements will be much greater than yours!
Yes, yes.
My good son. My good son.
You truly are Father's good son.
From now on, I'll be the king of the world.
And you can be the kid of the world.
All right.
I've had enough of you!
Father.
I grew up under your control.
And now, I am the king of the world.
Fine, you're the king of the world.
Father.
Rest in peace.
Rat!
Master Zhang.
It's been twenty years.
How did you get younger?
Mei Yuanhe,
since you've seen me,
why aren't you kneeling?
Rejuvenation!
It's the art of Rejuvenation!
Master Zhang, hurry and teach it to me!
I want immortality! I want to live forever!
This is my ultimate dream after all these years of tomb-raiding!
Have I gotten younger?
Let me see.
My hair has gotten thicker too.
Wake up!
Baihui at the crown, where all yang converges!
Clear the mind, unblock the blood and qi!
Screw you!
Are you okay?
Evil God!
Evil God, where are you?
Hurry and give me power!
Don't leave me!
Evil God!
Evil God, where are you?
Master Mei.
Are you clear-headed now?
No.
What just happened was real.
Now is the illusion!
You stepped on my clansman.
I want you to kneel and apologize to him.
I didn't do it on purpose!
Then you didn't mean what happened twenty years ago either?
Mei Yuanhe!
Don't you get it by now?
There is no Evil Entity at all.
It's all the Pathogens that have bred here for thousands of years.
They interfered with your senses
and magnified the desires in your hearts.
Obsession, greed, fear, and violence.
These are the greatest Evil Entities in people's hearts.
Master Mei,
I want you now
to face the skeletons of the Zhang clansmen here
and repent for what you did back then!
Speak!
What did you do to the Zhang clansmen back then?
Chun'er!
A golden hall!
Brother!
Wealth to rival a nation!
It's all mine!
Chun'er!
Brother!
Why are you guys here?
Didn't I tell you to go back?
Oh, you...
Father!
Enough!
It was us.
Back then, we disobeyed the Zhang family's orders
and had a falling out with the county warlord.
At the time,
we were a ragtag gang following the Dragon-Seeking Clan.
Seeing all that gold and treasure on the ground,
we thought we would be set for life.
Tell me,
who wouldn't be tempted by such wealth?
What happened next?